Mod f x square dx.
So please finish Percival
by next time.
I know many of you had this as
undergraduates, but it won't hurt to brush up.
Thank you, Steven.
I also put an advanced Fourier system
on the main hallway chalkboard.
And I'm hoping that one of you might
prove it by the end of the semester.
Now, the person to do so
will not only be in my good graces...
but also go on to fame and fortune...
by having their accomplishment
recorded and their name printed...
in the auspicious M.I.T. Tech.
Former winners include Nobel laureates,
Field's medal winners...
renowned astrophysicists
and lowly M.I.T. Professors.
Well, that's all.
If you have any questions,
I'm sure that Tom has the answers.
- Hi, Will.
- Kirsten, how you doing?
- I'm all right. How are you?
- Good.
- I didn't get on Cathy last night.
- No?
- No.
- Why not?
- I don't know. Cathy!
- What?
Why didn't you give me none of that nasty
little hoochie-woochie you usually throw at me?
Oh, fuck you and your Irish curse,
Chuckie.
Like I'd waste my energy spreadin'
my legs for that Tootsie Roll dick?
- So go home and give it a tug yourself.
- Tootsie Roll!
Toot-Toots!
She's missin' a tooth, Will.
She's got skin problems.
I don't...
Plus, it's like 5-to-2, Morgan ends
up marryin' her, you know what I mean?
There's only so many times you can bang
your friend's future wife.
It's wrong.
Where you goin'?
- I'm gonna take off.
- Fuck you, you're takin' off. It's like, what, 10:00?
I'm tired.
Irish curse?
She don't know.
There ain't no Irish curse.
- Out!
- Stop brushing me back.
Stop crowding the plate!
Which one will it be?
You're gonna get charged,
you know that.
You think I'm afraid of you, you big
fuck? You're crowdin' the fuckin' plate.
Hey, uh, Casey's bouncin' up a bar, uh, at
Harvard next week. We should go up there.
- What are we gonna do up there?
- I don't know.
We'll fuck up some smart kids.
You'll probably fit right in.
Ow! Fuckin' punk!
- Oh, what's up? You still tough?
- Come on!
- You want this?
- Ah, come on, come on. That's it.
I'd hold you forever here
In my arms
- Professor Lambeau?
- Yes?
I'm in your applied theories class. We're
all up at the math and science building.
Come here. It's Saturday!
Unless you want to have a drink
with me tonight.